SFU Archives reference and display materials collection
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- People Files, 1900 - 1998; F-247-3; 86 cm of textual records 466 photographs 3 contact sheets 7 negatives 2 slides 2 videocassettes: VHS 1 cassette tape and other material
  - Dawson, Catherine; 2 5x7; text, 1985; F-247-3-0-0-75 (Archival box - standard 247-18)
    Creator's original file classification code: M&PR SFU Week; Alumni.
  - Dawson, Graham; 10h Anniversary Chair; 3 5x7, 1974 - 1975; F-247-3-0-0-76 (Archival box - standard 247-18)
  - Dewick, Bernice; 8x10; text, 1981; F-247-3-0-0-77 (Archival box - standard 247-18)
    Creator's original file classification code: Comment, Spring 1981.
  - Dietrich, Ken; 5x7, [ca 1980]; F-247-3-0-0-78 (Archival box - standard 247-18)
  - Diewert, Gordon; 8x10, [ca 1980]; F-247-3-0-0-79 (Archival box - standard 247-18)
  - Dimma, William A., speaker for Gordon Lecture Series, Goals for Canada; 5x7, [ca 1980]; F-247-3-0-0-80 (Archival box - standard 247-18)
    Creator's original file classification code: M&PR?.
  - Doman, Herb; 5x7 color, [ca 1995]; F-247-3-0-0-81 (Archival box - standard 247-18)
  - Dunn, John; Animator, AVC; 8x10, [ca 1975]; F-247-3-0-0-82 (Archival box - standard 247-18)
  - Edge, Marc; 3x3, [197-]; F-247-3-0-0-83 (Archival box - standard 247-18)
  - Eidsvik, Phillip; former SFU student, BC Fisheries Survival Coalition, 1998; F-247-3-0-0-84 (Archival box - standard 247-18)
    Creator's original file classification code: Tri-City News.
  - Emery, Brian; 5x7, [ca 1975]; F-247-3-0-0-85 (Archival box - standard 247-18)
  - Enoch, Ted, [ca 1970]; F-247-3-0-0-86 (Archival box - standard 247-18)
  - Estrella, Miguel A.; text, 1983; F-247-3-0-0-87 (Archival box - standard 247-18)
    Creator's original file classification code: SFU Week, Sept. 29, 1983.
  - Fadl, Samia; Kinesiology and Engineering Science, 1984 - 1985; F-247-3-0-0-88 (Archival box - standard 247-18)
    Creator's original file classification code: SFU Week, May 10, 1984.
  - Fellman, Anita; Women's Studies; 8x10; news articles, 1977 - 1988; F-247-3-0-0-89 (Archival box - standard 247-18)
    Creator's original file classification code: SFU Week, Feb. 4, 18, 1988.
  - Felter, Jim; 5 5x7, 2 6x10, 8x20, 7x10;several news articles, 1979 - 1986; F-247-3-0-0-90 (Archival box - standard 247-18)
  - Findley, Marcia; Science Co-op Education; also Holly Findley, 1979 - 1989; F-247-3-0-0-91 (Archival box - standard 247-18)
  - Fisher, Ann; Audio Visual Resources Assistant; 8x10, 1967; F-247-3-0-0-92 (Archival box - standard 247-18)
    Creator's original file classification code: Audio Visual Centre: 19-9-67-4.
  - Flynn, Norah; Derrick Paul; Rieger, Harry Anthony; Town, Margaret Mary, 1988; F-247-3-0-0-93 (Archival box - standard 247-18)
  - Foulds, Sandra, [ca 1975]; F-247-3-0-0-94 (Archival box - standard 247-18)
  - Fox, Terry - 1 cassette: A Tribute to Terry Fox; 2 VHS videos: I Had a Dream, Every Step of the Way, 1979 - 1980; F-247-3-0-0-95 (Archival box - standard 247-19)
  - Fox, Terry - text, [197-]; F-247-3-0-0-96 (Archival box - standard 247-19)
    Creator's original file classification code: M&PR (edited by Archives).
  - Fox, Terry - photographs, 1977 - 1979; F-247-3-0-0-97 (Archival box - standard 247-19)
  - Fox, Terry - poster "The Terry Fox Legacy", 1995; F-247-3-0-0-98 (Archival box - standard 42-40)
  - Fraser, Simon - copies of family photographs, [ca 1900]; F-247-3-0-0-99 (Archival box - standard 247-19)
  - Fraser, Simon - explorer, text, [ca 1993]; F-247-3-0-0-100 (Archival box - standard 247-19)
  - Garr, Alan; Reporter in Province, Editor of Peak, Student Society Executive; 8x10, [ca 1980]; F-247-3-0-0-101 (Archival box - standard 247-19)
  - Gandhi; 7x9, [ca 1990]; F-247-3-0-0-102 (Archival box - standard 247-19)
    Creator's original file classification code: Peter Hulbert (Province).
  - Gibbons, Kate; Films, Tapes & Records Clerk, AVC, 1967; F-247-3-0-0-103 (Archival box - standard 247-19)
    Creator's original file classification code: Audio Visual Centre: 19-9-67.
  - Gidora, Mike; 4x4, [ca 1970]; F-247-3-0-0-104 (Archival box - standard 247-19)
  - Gillespie, David (with Robert Foottit); 3 5x7, 1980; F-247-3-0-0-105 (Archival box - standard 247-19)
    Creator's original file classification code: SFU Week Vol. 17, No. 2.
  - Glas, Ted; 4x4, [ca 1980]; F-247-3-0-0-106 (Archival box - standard 247-19)
  - Gohier, ?; 5x7, 1979; F-247-3-0-0-107 (Archival box - standard 247-19)
    Creator's original file classification code: SFU Week, Vol. 14, No. 10.
  - Grant, John; wheelchair sports; 8x10, [ca 1970]; F-247-3-0-0-108 (Archival box - standard 247-19)
  - Grauer, Dal; BC Shareholder's meeting; 2 8x10, 1959; F-247-3-0-0-109 (Archival box - standard 247-19)
  - Greenhough, Karen; dance choreographer, SFU; news articles, 1983; F-247-3-0-0-110 (Archival box - standard 247-19)
    Creator's original file classification code: Abbotsford, Sumas & Matsqui News.
  - Guns, Brian, video resident; 2x2, [ca 1970]; F-247-3-0-0-111 (Archival box - standard 247-19)
  - Haggerty, Sharon; SF Week Vol. 31, No. 10, March 14, 1985?, F-247-3-0-0-112 (Archival box - standard 247-19)
  - Hahn, Don, [ca 1980]; F-247-3-0-0-113 (Archival box - standard 247-19)
  - Hamilton, Charlotte Frances; 2 5x7, 1983; F-247-3-0-0-114 (Archival box - standard 247-19)
    Creator's original file classification code: SF Week, June 2, 1983.
  - Hara, Arthur, [199-]; F-247-3-0-0-115 (Archival box - standard 247-19)
  - Harris, Joel; 5x7, [ca 1980]; F-247-3-0-0-116 (Archival box - standard 247-19)
  - Hoffman, Joe, [ca 1980]; F-247-3-0-0-117 (Archival box - standard 247-19)
  - Houlihan, Barry; Football; 8x10, 1978; F-247-3-0-0-118 (Archival box - standard 247-19)
  - House, Rick; 2 8x10, 1978; F-247-3-0-0-119 (Archival box - standard 247-19)
  - Howell, Ann Marie; Biochemistry student; 2 5x7; news articles, 1983; F-247-3-0-0-120 (Archival box - standard 247-19)
    Creator's original file classification code: SF Week, Vol. 26, No. 5.
  - Hunter, Trenna; 6x10, 5x7, [ca 1975] - [ca 1980]; F-247-3-0-0-121 (Archival box - standard 247-19)
  - Hunwich, Richard; 3 5x7, 3 8x10, 1979 - 1980; F-247-3-0-0-122 (Archival box - standard 247-19)
    Creator's original file classification code: SFU Week, Vol. 17, No. 5.
  - Hurtig, Mel, [ca 1975]; F-247-3-0-0-123 (Archival box - standard 247-19)
  - Innis, Harold Adams; text, 1978 - 1977; F-247-3-0-0-124 (Archival box - standard 247-19)
  - Jewell, Ross; 2 5x7; text, 1974; F-247-3-0-0-125 (Archival box - standard 247-20)
    Creator's original file classification code: M&PR Comment 1974.
  - Joe, Grace; 2 5x7; text (Comment 1974), 1974 - 1985; F-247-3-0-0-126 (Archival box - standard 247-20)
    Creator's original file classification code: SF Week, Vol. 32, No. 5.
  - Johl, Randi; 5x7; text, [ca 1980]; F-247-3-0-0-127 (Archival box - standard 247-20)
  - Jones, Terry; text, 1983; F-247-3-0-0-128 (Archival box - standard 247-20)
    Creator's original file classification code: SF Week, Feb. 13, 1983.
  - Junta, Claude, [ca 1975]; F-247-3-0-0-129 (Archival box - standard 247-20)
  - Kamath, Shyam J.; 5x7; text, 1983; F-247-3-0-0-130 (Archival box - standard 247-20)
    Creator's original file classification code: SF Week.
  - Kaplin, Shane; 5x7; text, 1981; F-247-3-0-0-131 (Archival box - standard 247-20)
  - Kellock, Neil; 5x7; text, 1983; F-247-3-0-0-132 (Archival box - standard 247-20)
    Creator's original file classification code: SF Week, Vol. 26, No. 7.
  - Kelsey, Dr.; 5x7, [ca 1965]; F-247-3-0-0-133 (Archival box - standard 247-20)
  - King, Tom; 5x7 group photo with Hendy, Young, & unidentified woman, [ca 1969]; F-247-3-0-0-134 (Archival box - standard 247-20)
  - Kistiakowsky, George; text, 1973; F-247-3-0-0-135 (Archival box - standard 247-20)
  - Klassen, William; 3 5x7, text, 1972 - 1984; F-247-3-0-0-136 (Archival box - standard 247-20)
  - Knowlden, Peter; Financial Aid; 3x4, 1972; F-247-3-0-0-137 (Archival box - standard 247-20)
    Creator's original file classification code: Archives.
  - Knowles, Donald R.J.; biographical notes, 1971; F-247-3-0-0-138 (Archival box - standard 247-20)
  - Kronebusch, Eddy & Shelah; 3 5x7; text, 1989 - 1991; F-247-3-0-0-139 (Archival box - standard 247-20)
  - Krug, Kersti; Personnel; 5x8, [ca 1975]; F-247-3-0-0-140 (Archival box - standard 247-20)
  - Labonte, Ronald; 2 5x7; text, 1981; F-247-3-0-0-141 (Archival box - standard 247-20)
    Creator's original file classification code: SFU Week.
  - Lachs, Dr Manfred; text, 1976; F-247-3-0-0-142 (Archival box - standard 247-20)
    Creator's original file classification code: Comment.
  - Lambert, Allen; 2 5x7; text, 1982; F-247-3-0-0-143 (Archival box - standard 247-20)
    Creator's original file classification code: SFU Week, UNS.
  - LaPierre, Laurier; 3.5x5, [ca 1980]; F-247-3-0-0-144 (Archival box - standard 247-20)
  - Leach, Joy; BCSTA President; 3x5 + negative; text, 1984 - 1987; F-247-3-0-0-145 (Archival box - standard 247-20)
  - Lee, Dennis; 4x5, [ca 1975]; F-247-3-0-0-146 (Archival box - standard 247-20)
  - Lever, Walter; 3x5, 1974; F-247-3-0-0-147 (Archival box - standard 247-20)
  - Livingstone Jim (with George Pedersen); 5x7, 1979; F-247-3-0-0-148 (Archival box - standard 247-20)
  - Lord Fulton; 6x8, [ca 1980]; F-247-3-0-0-149 (Archival box - standard 247-20)
    Creator's original file classification code: Camera Press Ltd..
  - Lorimer, Paul; 4x5.5, [ca 1980]; F-247-3-0-0-150 (Archival box - standard 247-20)
  - Louie, Tong (Human Performance Centre); 4x6, [ca 1990]; F-247-3-0-0-151 (Archival box - standard 247-20)
  - Luke, Carmen; text, 1983; F-247-3-0-0-152 (Archival box - standard 247-20)
  - Lyttle, Clyve, [ca 1975]; F-247-3-0-0-153 (Archival box - standard 247-20)
  - Mackintosh, Alec; 5x7; text, 1984; F-247-3-0-0-154 (Archival box - standard 247-20)
    Creator's original file classification code: SF Week, Vol. 29, No. 3.
  - MacRae, Ted; Development Officer, [198-?]; F-247-3-0-0-155 (Archival box - standard 247-20)
    Creator's original file classification code: IMC?.
  - MacWilliam, David; 5x7, 1984; F-247-3-0-0-156 (Archival box - standard 247-20)
  - Madden, John (with Pat McGeer & George Pedersen; 2 5x7), 1983; F-247-3-0-0-157 (Archival box - standard 247-20)
  - Madrid, Galindo; 2.5x2.5, 1975; F-247-3-0-0-158 (Archival box - standard 247-20)
  - Magarrell, Gary W.; text, 1982; F-247-3-0-0-159 (Archival box - standard 247-20)
    Creator's original file classification code: SFU People.
  - Mah, Keith; 5x7, [ca 1980]; F-247-3-0-0-160 (Archival box - standard 247-20)
  - Mainwaring, Brian; 5x7, 1974; F-247-3-0-0-161 (Archival box - standard 247-20)
  - Marling, Phyllis; 8x10, [ca 1980]; F-247-3-0-0-162 (Archival box - standard 247-20)
    Creator's original file classification code: Graphic Industries.
  - Matsen, ?; 5x7, [ca 1970]; F-247-3-0-0-163 (Archival box - standard 247-20)
  - McBride, Anita; Allied Chemical Award; 3 5x7, 2 8x10, 1980; F-247-3-0-0-164 (Archival box - standard 247-20)
  - McCoach, Stephen, Co-op student (with Liisa Atva); 5x7, text, 1984; F-247-3-0-0-165 (Archival box - standard 247-20)
  - McFetridge, Paul; 4 5x7, 1982; F-247-3-0-0-166 (Archival box - standard 247-20)
    Creator's original file classification code: SFU Week, Vol. 22, No. 2.
  - McGeer, David; 2 5x7, 1980; F-247-3-0-0-167 (Archival box - standard 247-20)
  - McGeer, Dr. Patrick; 7 5x7, 8x10; text, 1981 - 1983; F-247-3-0-0-168 (Archival box - standard 247-20)
  - McGregor, Dr. Ian; 2 5x7; text, 1980 - 1989; F-247-3-0-0-169 (Archival box - standard 247-20)
  - McInnes, John; text, 1982; F-247-3-0-0-170 (Archival box - standard 247-20)
  - McIntosh, Patricia; 5x7, 1979; F-247-3-0-0-171 (Archival box - standard 247-20)
  - McLaren, Juliet; 3 5x7, text, 1982; F-247-3-0-0-172 (Archival box - standard 247-20)
    Creator's original file classification code: SFU Week, June 3, 1982.
  - McQuiggan, Kevin; 2 5x7; text, 1979 - 1983; F-247-3-0-0-173 (Archival box - standard 247-20)
    Creator's original file classification code: UNS, SFU Week, June 1983.
  - Melody, Dr. William; 2 5x7, 8x10; text, 1978 - 1989; F-247-3-0-0-174 (Archival box - standard 247-21)
  - Millen, Bruce; 5x7, text, 1983; F-247-3-0-0-175 (Archival box - standard 247-21)
    Creator's original file classification code: SF Week, Vol. 27, No. 7.
  - Miller, Terry; 4x4, 3 5x7, text, 1978; F-247-3-0-0-176 (Archival box - standard 247-21)
    Creator's original file classification code: SF Week, Vol. 12, No. 9.
  - Mittleman, Karen; Grad student, Kinesiology; 5x7, text, 1986; F-247-3-0-0-177 (Archival box - standard 247-21)
    Creator's original file classification code: SF Week, Vol. 36, No. 11.
  - Moeser, Shannon, PhD in psychology; 3 contact sheets, 1971; F-247-3-0-0-178 (Archival box - standard 247-21)
  - Moser, Gail; text, 1981 - 1982; F-247-3-0-0-179 (Archival box - standard 247-21)
  - Muckle, Rob; 2 5x7; text, 1983; F-247-3-0-0-180 (Archival box - standard 247-21)
    Creator's original file classification code: SF Week, Columbian.
  - Musgrave, Susan, 1970; F-247-3-0-0-181 (Archival box - standard 247-21)
  - Neilson, Elizabeth; Entomological Society of America award; 5x7, text, 1981; F-247-3-0-0-182 (Archival box - standard 247-21)
    Creator's original file classification code: SFU Week, Vol. 21, No. 4.
  - Nelson, Donald; SFU student, Commonwealth Scholarship winner; 5x7, 1976; F-247-3-0-0-183 (Archival box - standard 247-21)
  - Newman, Gerald; text, 1983; F-247-3-0-0-184 (Archival box - standard 247-21)
    Creator's original file classification code: The Province.
  - Ng, Kam Ling Evelyn; text, 1989; F-247-3-0-0-185 (Archival box - standard 247-21)
  - Nowlan, Alden, [ca 1975]; F-247-3-0-0-186 (Archival box - standard 247-21)
  - Page, Malcolm (photocopy - see Melody Rudd), [ca 1970]; F-247-3-0-0-188 (Archival box - standard 247-21)
  - Parent, Madelene, CCC organizer; 5x7, [ca 1980]; F-247-3-0-0-189 (Archival box - standard 247-21)
  - Parkin, Derek; Graphic artist; 8x10, 1967; F-247-3-0-0-190 (Archival box - standard 247-21)
  - Patterson, Bruce; 2 5x7; text, 1985; F-247-3-0-0-191 (Archival box - standard 247-21)
    Creator's original file classification code: SF Week Spotlight.
  - Pawlovich, Kerry; Manpower; 5x8, [ca 1972]; F-247-3-0-0-192 (Archival box - standard 247-21)
  - Peter, Laurence; 8x10 (with Walt Griba?), [ca 1980]; F-247-3-0-0-193 (Archival box - standard 247-21)
  - Peterson, Gordon; 2 5x7; text, 1983; F-247-3-0-0-194 (Archival box - standard 247-21)
  - Petroff, Norman; 3 5x7 (with Susan Jamieson-McLarnon, Mayor Gordon Campbell); text, 1988; F-247-3-0-0-195 (Archival box - standard 247-21)
  - Pinder, Janet; 2 5x7; SF Week, June 2, 1983, F-247-3-0-0-196 (Archival box - standard 247-21)
  - Popma, Anne; 5 5x7, 8x10; text, 1980 - 1986; F-247-3-0-0-197 (Archival box - standard 247-21)
  - Powley, Mike; 4x5, 1982; F-247-3-0-0-198 (Archival box - standard 247-21)
  - Priest, Simon; news (SF Week story, Nov. 10, 1982), 1982 - 1983; F-247-3-0-0-199 (Archival box - standard 247-21)
  - Provan, Dr. Keith Geoffrey; curriculum vitae, 1985; F-247-3-0-0-200 (Archival box - standard 247-21)
  - Raines, Marke; 7x10, [ca 1975]; F-247-3-0-0-201 (Archival box - standard 247-21)
  - Rankin, Harry; 3.5x3.5, [ca 1970]; F-247-3-0-0-202 (Archival box - standard 247-21)
    Creator's original file classification code: JoAnn Kronquist.
  - Reed, Jean; 5x7, [ca 1975]; F-247-3-0-0-203 (Archival box - standard 247-21)
  - Rimmer, Karen; dance resident; 21.5x21.5, [ca 1975]; F-247-3-0-0-204 (Archival box - standard 247-21)
  - Roberts, Kathleen A. Bell-Irving; (niece of BC Lt. Governor); Shrum Gold Medal winner, 1978; F-247-3-0-0-205 (Archival box - standard 247-21)
    Creator's original file classification code: SFU Week, Vol. 11, No. 4.
  - Roberts, Stan; former VP Development; 2 5x5, 5x7; text, 1977 - 1978; F-247-3-0-0-206 (Archival box - standard 247-21)
  - Robertson, Barb; 2 5x7, [ca 1975]; F-247-3-0-0-207 (Archival box - standard 247-21)
  - Robertson, Bob; CKNW; United Way, 1981; F-247-3-0-0-208 (Archival box - standard 247-21)
  - Rowgow, Sally; Behavioural Sciences Foundation; 3x3, 1970; F-247-3-0-0-209 (Archival box - standard 247-21)
    Creator's original file classification code: M&PR, Comment.
  - Ross, John A., St. Andrew's Principal; 3.5x4.5, [ca 1975]; F-247-3-0-0-210 (Archival box - standard 247-21)
    Creator's original file classification code: UBC.
  - Roy, Ron; IBM Rep with George Pedersen; 2 5x7, [ca 1979]; F-247-3-0-0-211 (Archival box - standard 247-21)
  - Rudd, Melody; 2 8x10 (1 with Malcolm Page), [ca 1970]; F-247-3-0-0-212 (Archival box - standard 247-21)
  - Ryarson; 3.5x5, [ca 1980]; F-247-3-0-0-213 (Archival box - standard 247-21)
  - Salter, Helen; Engineering; 5x7, [ca 1978]; F-247-3-0-0-214 (Archival box - standard 247-22)
  - Sass, Robert; Industrial Relations now Department of Labour, SK; 5x7, 1978; F-247-3-0-0-215 (Archival box - standard 247-22)
  - Sawyer, Marg; Registrar's Office; 3x5, 5x7 (with Diane Crowe); text, 1987; F-247-3-0-0-216 (Archival box - standard 247-22)
    Creator's original file classification code: M&PR, June 18, 1987; Alumni Journal 1987.
  - Sayal, Rakesh; 1.5x4, [ca 1975]; F-247-3-0-0-217 (Archival box - standard 247-22)
  - Schiffer, Roger; 5x7, [ca 1980]; F-247-3-0-0-218 (Archival box - standard 247-22)
  - Seeley, John; 3.5x5, 1968; F-247-3-0-0-219 (Archival box - standard 247-22)
  - Sens, Al; 8x10, [ca 1980]; F-247-3-0-0-220 (Archival box - standard 247-22)
  - Shillow, Moshe; Science student meeting; 3x4, [ca 1970]; F-247-3-0-0-221 (Archival box - standard 247-22)
  - Siegler, Karl; 5x7, [ca 1970]; F-247-3-0-0-222 (Archival box - standard 247-22)
  - Simson, Bernd;Physics grad and holography researcher; 5x7, [ca 1970]; F-247-3-0-0-223 (Archival box - standard 247-22)
  - Sinclair, Rosalind; 2 color slides, [ca 1967]; F-247-3-0-0-224 (Archival box - standard 247-22)
    Creator's original file classification code: Horst Ehricht.
  - Sinnott, Ted; photographs, text, [ca 1975] - [ca 1985]; F-247-3-0-0-225 (Archival box - standard 247-22)
    Textual records; Photographic materials
  - Skulski, David; 2.5x2, [ca 1975]; F-247-3-0-0-226 (Archival box - standard 247-22)
  - Smiechowski, Zenon; 8x10, [ca 1980]; F-247-3-0-0-227 (Archival box - standard 247-22)
  - Smith, Alan P.D.; Assistant to the President; 5x7, 1967; F-247-3-0-0-228 (Archival box - standard 247-22)
  - Smith, Margaret; news articles, 1982; F-247-3-0-0-229 (Archival box - standard 247-22)
    Creator's original file classification code: SF Week, Sept 23, 1982.
  - Smith, Thomas J.; Visiting professor, Kinesiology; text, 1975; F-247-3-0-0-230 (Archival box - standard 247-22)
  - Speers, Edith; 3x4, [ca 1975]; F-247-3-0-0-231 (Archival box - standard 247-22)
  - Spicer, Keith; Professor; news article, 1983; F-247-3-0-0-232 (Archival box - standard 247-22)
    Creator's original file classification code: The London Free Press.
  - Stacey, Carolyn, 1983; F-247-3-0-0-233 (Archival box - standard 247-22)
  - St. Amand, Jan, 1983; F-247-3-0-0-234 (Archival box - standard 247-22)
    Creator's original file classification code: Flare Magazine.
  - Stark, John; news articles, 1983; F-247-3-0-0-235 (Archival box - standard 247-22)
    Creator's original file classification code: Calgary Herald, Aldergrove Star.
  - Steadman, Tracy (with George Pedersen); 8x10, 1979; F-247-3-0-0-236 (Archival box - standard 247-22)
  - Summers, Gordon M.; 5 3x3, [ca 1980]; F-247-3-0-0-237 (Archival box - standard 247-22)
  - Swan, Gerry; Track coach; news articles, 1988; F-247-3-0-0-238 (Archival box - standard 247-22)
  - Swaters, Gordon Edwin; Mathematics; curriculum vitae, 1989; F-247-3-0-0-239 (Archival box - standard 247-22)
  - Tarr, Sharon; Wrist wrestler and Staff (mail room); 2 5x7; text, 1989; F-247-3-0-0-240 (Archival box - standard 247-23)
  - Thom, Gordon; President, BCIT; text, 1985; F-247-3-0-0-241 (Archival box - standard 247-23)
  - Thomas, Audrey; Writer-in-Residence; 5x7, news articles, 1981 - 1982; F-247-3-0-0-242 (Archival box - standard 247-23)
  - Thornburg, Jonathan; Honors student, math & physics; 2 5x7, text, 1983; F-247-3-0-0-243 (Archival box - standard 247-23)
  - Timberlake, Alan; 4x4, [ca 1975]; F-247-3-0-0-244 (Archival box - standard 247-23)
  - Toor, John, [ca 1970]; F-247-3-0-0-245 (Archival box - standard 247-23)
  - Town, Florida; Staff, M 9 5x7, 2 8x10; articles, 1979 - 1991; F-247-3-0-0-246 (Archival box - standard 247-23)
  - Trotter, Dave, M.Sc. Grad; 2 5x7, article, 1981; F-247-3-0-0-247 (Archival box - standard 247-23)
    Creator's original file classification code: M&PR, June 1981.
  - Trudeau, Pierre Elliott; 6.5x7.5, 8x10, 1971 - 1973; F-247-3-0-0-248 (Archival box - standard 247-23)
    Creator's original file classification code: Jim Banham (UBC).
  - Tuner, Ed; Public Relations Officer; 2 8x10 (in white shirt foreground left profile), 1966; F-247-3-0-0-249 (Archival box - standard 247-23)
    Creator's original file classification code: Audio Visual Centre, 66018-48D.
  - Vanel, Kurtis; 8x10, 4.5x6.5 (Doug Gyseman, Recording Technician, UBC), [ca 1967]; F-247-3-0-0-250 (Archival box - standard 247-23)
    Creator's original file classification code: Audio Visual Centre, 19-9-67-11.
  - Vulliamy, Mark; 2.5x3.5, [ca 1967]; F-247-3-0-0-251 (Archival box - standard 247-23)
  - Wah, Fred; 5x7, [ca 1970]; F-247-3-0-0-252 (Archival box - standard 247-23)
    Wah, Fred; Textual records
  - Walker, Randy; 4x5, [ca 1975] - [ca 1976]; F-247-3-0-0-253 (Archival box - standard 247-23)
  - Waters, Commander; 5x7, [ca 1980]; F-247-3-0-0-254 (Archival box - standard 247-23)
  - Whalley, George; 5x7, [ca 1980]; F-247-3-0-0-255 (Archival box - standard 247-23)
  - Williams, Ian; ACS; 4 5x7; SFU Week articles, 1985 - 1989; F-247-3-0-0-256 (Archival box - standard 247-23)
  - Wilson, Chief Justice John Owen; article from The Sun, 1969; F-247-3-0-0-257 (Archival box - standard 247-23)
  - Woolley, Mel; 8x10, [ca 1975]; F-247-3-0-0-258 (Archival box - standard 247-23)
    Creator's original file classification code: P. Knowlden.
  - Wosk, Morris J.; 5x7, 1996; F-247-3-0-0-259 (Archival box - standard 247-23)
    Creator's original file classification code: SF News, June 6, 1996.
  - Wyman, Jake; contact sheet, negatives (include Sandra Foulds), [ca 1972]; F-247-3-0-0-260 (Archival box - standard 247-23)
  - Yates, Michael J.; 3.3; Vancouver poet?, [ca 1970]; F-247-3-0-0-261 (Archival box - standard 247-23)
    Creator's original file classification code: Lois Siegel.
  - Young, ?; 5x7 (see also group photo King, Tom with Hendy and unidentified woman), [ca 1970]; F-247-3-0-0-262 (Archival box - standard 247-23)
    Creator's original file classification code: UNS 04/1.69.
- Subject Files, [ca 1870] - 2000; F-247-4; 1.24 m of textual records 1305 photographs 91 contact sheets 204 negatives 129 slides 15 sketches
  Series consists of drawings, photos, contact sheets, slides, negatives, publications, notes, correspondence, news releases, memorabilia, photocopies, and pamphlets relating to subject files kept by the Media and Public Relations Office to keep track of ideas, news leads, and developing stories as they relate to SFU. See access points for a list of SFU departments and organizations represented in the files.
  Simon Fraser University Pipe Band; Purcell String Quartet; Jinan University (China); Simon Fraser University Women's Centre; Simon Fraser University Theatre; Simon Fraser University Gallery; Simon Fraser Student Society; Peak Publications Society; University Library; Archives and Records Management Department; Facilities Services
  - 25 Years of Change anniversary photos with text, 1965 - 1990; F-247-4-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 247-24)
    Creator's original file classification code: Various.